I'm going to call the order of this regular meeting of the modern special utility authority
for today's date in time.
I don't have done it on the agenda's invocation by the pastor of First United Methodist Church.
Mark Wright, and Mark, thanks for being here tonight.
My pleasure to know, next to the pit boy, I said.
I'm going to call off the class, but I think it's a great pleasure to be here.
Thank you so much for the gift of this life and for the awareness or the beliefs that you
do not pop us here, to spend our lives in endless diversion and confusion, but that you
call us to work together, to build a life together, to build and to seek and long for
community.
We give thanks for those who have stepped forward to offer leadership and direction in this particular
We ask that you would help them and help us all work together to build a community of safety and peace
and harmony.
May that be up or most in all that we do in sight, not just in this meeting, but to our days and our weeks
and our lives here.
We pray this with the sense of gratitude for this opportunity and for the gift of life
itself.
Your son's name, Luke.
Amen.
Please join in the play.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America, and to the Republic for which it stands,
one nation under God, in the name of Israel, in the name of the State of Justice, to
all.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hi.
I'm three.
Our excuse me.
I don't know if there was public input on the schedule of personal appearances or in the audience, it
was to address the authority on any of the agenda items.
If being non item five is being considered agenda staff is recommending item six to
eight for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions, I'd entertain a motion to approve.
Most deferred.
And a second, please.
Second.
We'll call.
Jonathan.
All right.
Four.
Five.
That's one that we had catch fire.
You're my son.
I'm here to go through check everything out.
Do a Blimmer and cost estimate.
And they will do compares on design.
So we can do an outdoor indoor station in just your room and the best and the cost of
weight.
For us to rebuild that.
It was in the right steady.
Future years to look at redoing.
And this will quote annual rule number 12 tolerance just part of current up our umbrella
relationship with us.
It is.
to really take a large look at everything we're saying and this is just a segment of that, correct?
Yes, sir. Any questions for Tyler?
No.
So we need a most to approve work on number 12.
Is there?
So there we have a second.
Second.
We'll call this.
So, I, for instance.
Weston Lewis Johnson and now we have before us also the associate's work world third team for the design of the nickel substation also known as substation to Tyler
Yes, sir, so this is the actual design
And specifications and everything for substation number two or nickel substation
We we had also come down to a cost estimate on this substation. They give us two different designs and outdoor stations similar to sub three on Rockdale
In indoor station in similar to how it's currently is
What the indoor was approximate three million dollars plus some other items such as land acquisition
GRDA maybe me during and everything
Just some things incidental cost maybe our feeders new feeders and they also compared the
Apped war which is similar to sub three in a came in at four million dollars plus the added extras
So based on that staff has decided that we would like to do indoor similar to how currently is and with this they with the approval of this. They will design
sub to
According to indoor station
So we're one step further along. Yes, sir. This station
Yes, we've already done the preliminary estimates and now we're moving more on the base okay, and
Again, this is something that was recommended as part of the rate study
Yes, sir that actual engineering was budgeted this year in our budget
So we're just when you get a jump on and get going and Dean was assuming that we move forward with this project
How are we going to fund it the estimation is that we would do a bond issue not this fiscal year but the fiscal year after
Okay, is what the plan is in the right study
I know that I talked to Jill a little bit ago
I think that Jill and Tyler and I they have a couple of alternatives along that line
But ultimately, he'll be paid for by the rates and that's the reason we had the rate study is to when we do the rate adjustments
That it would be able to recover these costs
Okay
Any questions for Tyler on a gender item 10
And I believe I read it somewhere around the end of December when this will be finished
Yes, sir, okay, and the one that we just noticed they started go back. It was it's April April. Okay, minute, minute, minute
Okay, so you see the timing of it is such that when we have that end then we'll be starting to look together next year's budget anyway
And that's when we would be putting together information about the rate adjustments and possibly going into the long market
In the other questions
I think to clarify that the nickel substation the age on that Tyler
It's there it's the actual transformers are a ride in 1972
So, we've got our
All of our money for the board in that year
I think so I know three people sitting around there that we'll watch his team
Well, we have a motion to approve, work order 13.
One second.
Motion.
Johnson.
Jolly.
Forster.
Question.
Lewis.
Hi.
I have 13 newbies.
Do you guys need anything?
No.
I have not enough of this agenda.
Okay.
Staff, unfortunately, packet.
Now, I'm available for questions.
If there are no questions, we'll move on to a trusty community announcements.
Any announcements?
Anyone?
If not, do we have a motion to adjourn the issue, Amy?
Motion adjourn.
Second, please.
We'll call.
Western.
Lewis.
Four.
Five.
Johnson.